Vengeance bites back.
Slayers is a horror, comedy, fantasy film directed by K. Asher Levin.
A group of superstar influencers are drawn to a reclusive billionaire's mansion
only to find themselves trapped in the lair of an evil vampire.
The only way out is to be saved by a famous online
gamer and an old school vampire hunter.
Elliot Jones, played by Thomas Jane.
Jules, played by Abigail Breslin.
Beverly Rektor, played by Malin Åkerman.
Flynn, played by Kara Hayward.
Liz, played by Lydia Hearst.
Steven Rektor, played by Adam Ambruso.
Slayers is a 2022 American comedy horror film,
written, produced and directed by K.
Asher Levin.
It stars Thomas Jane, Kara Hayward, Jack Donnelly, Lydia
Hearst, Malin Akerman, and Abigail Breslin.
The film was released in theaters and digitally on
October 21, 2022, by The Avenue Entertainment.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.